export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2019 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1812q.pdf",
        solution: "1901a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yıldırım", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1901q.pdf",
        solution: "1902a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Susanne Tegler", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Dovran Nurgeldiyev", affiliation: "Magtumguly Turkmen State University, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Berkay Unlu", affiliation: "Dokuz Eylül University, İzmir" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Asude Ebrar Kızıloğlu", affiliation: "Özel Kadıköy Eğitmen Fen ve Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "İrem Nur Çevikcan", affiliation: "Buca Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1902q.pdf",
        solution: "1903a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Ensar Göktekin", affiliation: "Malatya Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Shin Min Hyeok", affiliation: "Geoje Island, South Korea" },
            { name: "M. Lütfi Yarar", affiliation: "İstanbul Technical University" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Roushen Ovezmuradov", affiliation: "Ashgabat, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Osman Asil", affiliation: "Ege University, İzmir" },
            { name: "Muhammet Habip Bingöl", affiliation: "İstanbul University" },
            { name: "Sten Hemmingsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Asude Ebrar Kızıloğlu", affiliation: "Özel Kadıköy Eğitmen Fen ve Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "İrem Nur Çevikcan", affiliation: "Buca Tırnaklı Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Sude Filiz", affiliation: "İzmir Bilfen Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Feray Lina Yence", affiliation: "Buca Tırnaklı Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "UNIST, South Korea" },
            { name: "Berkay Unlu", affiliation: "Dokuz Eylül University, İzmir" },
            { name: "Max Nilsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Oktay Balkış", affiliation: "Aksaray Abdülhamid Han Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Animoku Abdulwahab", affiliation: "Abuja, Nigeria" },
            { name: "Paolo Perfetti", affiliation: "Universite degli studi di Tor Vergata Roma, Italy" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Vanio Beccaccioli", affiliation: "Terni, Italy" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Bülent Doğru", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Johan Sandell", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Eren Can Kızıldağ", affiliation: "Massachusetts Insıtute of Technology, USA" },
            { name: "Dovran Nurgeldiyev", affiliation: "Magtumguly Turkmen State University, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Metin Can Aydemir", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Berkay Kırali", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Mustafa Serdar İpek", affiliation: "Üsküdar, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Alper Bahcekapılı", affiliation: "Evrensel Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Tuğşad Koyuncu", affiliation: "Fethiye Ömer Özyer Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Allen Druze", affiliation: "Gulf Stream School, Florida, USA" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1903q.pdf",
        solution: "1904a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Max Nilsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Halil Alperen Gözeten", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Hakan Karakuş", affiliation: "Antalya Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi, Antalya" },
            { name: "Mustafa Emir Çelebi", affiliation: "İstanbul Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Ender Doğan Işık", affiliation: "Final Okulları, Ankara" },
            { name: "İbrahim Suat Evren", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Ömer Topaloğlu", affiliation: "Özel İzmir Fen Lisesi, İzmir" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1904q.pdf",
        solution: "1905a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Murat Chashmetov", affiliation: "TSU Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Bora Ege Duygun", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Max Nilsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismanıng, Germany" },
            { name: "İrem Nur Çevikcan", affiliation: "Buca İnci Özer Tırnaklı Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Feray Lina Yence", affiliation: "Buca İnci Özer Tırnaklı Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Asude Ebrar Kızıloğlu", affiliation: "Kadıköy Özel Eğitmen Fen ve Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Sude Filiz", affiliation: "İzmir Bilfen Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Ayşe Zehra Şen", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1905q.pdf",
        solution: "1906a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismanıng, Germany" },
            { name: "Mehmet Yeni", affiliation: "Tarsus, Mersin" },
            { name: "Max Nilsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Halil Özkan", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Bora Ege Duygun", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Halil Alperen Gözeten", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Demir Eken", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Bilge Köksal", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Ozan Kaymak", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Hakan Karakuş", affiliation: "Antalya Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Ömer Topaloğlu", affiliation: "Özel İzmir Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Mustafa Emir Çelebi", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "İbrahim Suat Evren", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Enes Özdemır", affiliation: "Buca İnci Özer Tırnaklı Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "John Wright", affiliation: "Brooklyn, New York, USA" },
            { name: "Jürgen Weith", affiliation: "University of Applied Sciences, Schweinfurt, Germany" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1906q.pdf",
        solution: "1908a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Max Nilsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Halil Özkan", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Halil Alperen Gözeten", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1908q.pdf",
        solution: "1909a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Ramil Jabiyev", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Emre Karabıyık", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Xagani Gasımov", affiliation: "Baku, Azerbaijan" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Halil Özkan", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "İbrahim Suat Evren", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Halil Alperen Gözeten", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Ozan Kaymak", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Hakan Karakuş", affiliation: "Antalya Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Enes Özdemır", affiliation: "METU, Ankara" },
            { name: "Kaan Yolcu", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Yusuf Kaan Çiçekdağ", affiliation: "Özel Bornova Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mustafa Emir Çelebi", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1909q.pdf",
        solution: "1910a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Fatih Demir", affiliation: "Çapa Fen Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Ramil Jabiyev", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Hakan Karakuş", affiliation: "Antalya Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi, Antalya" },
            { name: "Buca Tırnaklı", affiliation: "Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "İbrahim Suat Evren", affiliation: "Denizli Özel Denizli Koleji, Denizli" },
            { name: "Enes Özdemir", affiliation: "Buca Tırnaklı Fen Lisesi" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1910q.pdf",
        solution: "1911a.pdf",
        solvers: [{ name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" }]
    },
    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2019,
        question: "1911q.pdf",
        solution: "1912a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Emirhan Yağcıoğlu", affiliation: "Matematik ve Fen Bilimleri Anadolu Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Muti Kara", affiliation: "Ankara Atatürk Anadolu Lisesi" },
            {
                name: "Gizem Tabak",
                affiliation: "University of İllinois at Urbana-Campaign’d, USA"
            },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong Kong, China" },
            { name: "Barış Koyuncu", affiliation: "Özel Enka Lisesi, İstinye, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Ramil Jabiyev", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mountassir Farid", affiliation: "Awalee Consulting, Paris, France" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Zarmehr Zarifi", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    }
];
